amaltv.net 2018-04-27

# AmalTV :: Info » Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes the types of information that AmalTV collects on the Site. AmalTV reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of the current posted privacy policy. If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact Amal via Contact form or by sending email to [amal@amaltv.com](mailto:amal@amaltv.com)

**\- What Information We Gather..**  
We track and store any information you enter on our website. You can choose not to provide certain information, but this will limit you from using full features of the site such as marking shows as favorite. We also store video watching history of any user who visit our site We do not use "cookies" to save information or any other purpose, but Facebook™ may store some cookies to track and save Login details etc; to AmalTV. We also use Visitor Tracking programs like Google Analytics and any data tracked by Analytics™ will not be monitored by AmalTV Staff. 

**\- How do we use the data we stored..**  
We DO NOT sell or give away any of users' data under any circumstance. we just use those data to analyze our site performance as well as analyzes for future developments of the site. also notice registered users may occassionally receive news leters via Email & believe us, we don't Spam! 

**\- With whom do we share your information..**  
We do not share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties, except when required by law enforcement or judicial authorities which may occur from time to time. In this case, we will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena in order to assist a law enforcement investigation. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

**\- Information relating to children..**  
AmalTV may accessed and used by anybody in any age. there are no any age restrictions inside the website. We, AmalTV take our best effort to keep the site suits for anybody in any age both by content and convenience. Please note AmalTV use Google AdSense™ to display Ads on the site, so the content of the advertisement from Google may be vary time to time. at the time Google AdSense display Adverts which are suitable for anybody. we do not have control over those externally loaded content, Please visit [Google AdWords Terms](http://support.google.com/adwords/certification/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=151875) page to check latest terms of content displayed via Google AdSense
